beestar.org 2018-08-31

# Beestar.org - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

| Last updated March 1, 2004  
---|---  
  
Beestar Educations provides online educational programs to grade school students. Beestar is committed to the privacy and security of our users. This policy statement tells you how we use the information collected from you. We require all users read and agree our privacy policy before using Beestar services. 

**Parent Permission**

Our learning services for children are provided through parent (guardian) subscriptions. A young student must have parents' permission to use Beestar services. Parents are responsible to explain our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy to young users. In general, Beestar only contact parents for exercise status and event notifications.

**Information We Collect from You**

Beestar requests only minimum information from our customers for providing services. Beestar will not give your contact information (such as email, phone number, and postal address) to any third party. 

We send email or letter to you only when necessary such as registration confirmation, exercise result reports, and site event notifications. 

To encourage high standards in academic studies, we periodically recognize students with significant achievements in our educational programs. We may write news or post honor rolls with such students' name, school name, and achievement information on our sites. We do not show personal contact information of our users. If our news story covers a student, we will let the parent review the content before publishing it. We do so in good faith to recognize students' achievements in our community. All Beestar users have agreed to use our site information for good and harmless purpose. 

**Links to Other Sites**

Beestar sites may contain links to other web sites whose content we believe will be of possible interest and value to our customers. 

We do not control the content of third-party sites. Once you leave our servers, the use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you're visiting. That policy may differ from ours. Beestar is not responsible for any consequences you get from other web sites.

We recommend that parents guide their children in visiting new web sites.

**Security**

Beestar sites and services are password-protected so that only authorized users are permitted to access them or view the member information relevant to the accounts. We strongly recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Beestar does not ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Beestar is not responsible for any consequences resulted from other people logged into your account with the right password.

Remember to sign out of your Beestar password-protected account and/or close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information if your computer is accessible to others, if you share a computer with someone else, or if you are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet café. 

The importance of security for your personally identifiable information is of utmost concern to us. Unfortunately, data transmission over the Internet is not guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Beestar cannot and does not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you transmit information at your own risk. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online — for example, via our message board — that information can be collected and used by people you do not know. While Beestar strives to protect its customers' personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you choose to disclose online and you do so at your own risk. 

Beestar's Privacy Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Beestar's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. 

**Notification of Changes**

Beestar periodically reviews and enhances this Privacy Policy as necessary. This policy might change as Beestar updates and expands its services. We will post notice on our sites about such changes prior to implementing the new practice(s). 

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using Beestar sites, you signify your consent to the Beestar's Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this, please do not use our web sites or services. Your continued use of Beestar web sites or services following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes in accordance with our Terms of Use.
